SOUTH KOREA CRUSADE WITH T.B. JOSHUA
HEALING CONTINUES
Please, Father, heal me!
I had an accident and my arm and leg were affected.
Because I don't have any cartilage in my knee, whenever I walk, it is so painful.
I cannot walk!
Please, heal me!
I want to run; please, heal me!
Prayer Line at the South Korea Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 1
Healing in Jesus' Name
Healed in Jesus' Name
Thank You, Father!
Overjoyed at her healing, she marches and even jogs, giving thanks to the Saviour.
What a remarkable healing from a remarkable God!
SOUTH KOREA CRUSADE WITH T.B. JOSHUA
TESTIMONY TIME
Lee Hyun Ju - Deajeon, South Korea
Good morning. My name is Lee Hyun Ju. I am from Deajeon in South Korea.
One and a half years ago, I had an accident.
I sustained a fracture in my right leg and shoulder.
Unfortunately, I had an operation.
During the operation, I had iron rods inserted
and after one year, they were removed by another operation.
During my rehabilitation, the doctors discovered that I had no cartilage in my right knee.
The doctor told me that due to the inflammation, I could develop severe rheumatism.
The rehabilitation did not solve the problem.
It greatly affected my daily activities.
About one and a half years ago, I had a severe accident.
Because of that, I had to undergo an operation.
I went for rehabilitation because I was experiencing severe pain and I had no other choice.
Even though I went for rehabilitation, the pain remained the same and I also then experienced other problems.
So, I went to the doctor again, and he told me that there were more problems.
The doctor said that due to the inflammation, I was a hundred percent likely to develop rheumatism.
The doctor told me that I would suffer from rheumatism.
South Korea Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Testimony Time
Due to the accident, I had a fracture to my right leg and shoulder.
The doctor said that the joints of my right leg had been seriously shattered.
It really affected my daily activities.
I received the promise of God concerning my problem, through this crusade.
So, I came to this crusade.
It is for more than one and a half years that I suffered from this pain.
Because of this pain, I could not walk or stand for a long time.
There were a lot of problems in my daily life.
Because I could not walk, I could not go out.
I needed somebody to help me. My condition caused me to become depressed.
Without the assistance of my family members, I could not do anything.
Basically, I could not walk or stand for a long time.
Therefore, I could not go out very often.
Because of the pain, without the help of my family, I could not walk, stand or go somewhere.
Because I had a problem with my arm, I could not work.
Especially when I am working, I make a lot of use of my arms.
But because of this accident, I had to quit my job.
I went to several hospitals in search of a solution.
I also went to church and prayed without the belief that I could receive healing.
First of all, I went to the hospital and I also went to church and prayed
but I didn't think that it would really help me.
The doctor told me to avoid using my knees
and that I should wear the recommended leg brace.
Because of the severe pain, the doctor told me to use the knee brace.
When she came to the crusade, tell us what actually happened. What took place?
South Korea Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Testimony Time
I had the confidence and faith that God would heal me this time.
I had the faith that God would heal me.
When Prophet T.B. Joshua prayed for me, I felt the light of the Holy Spirit touch my whole body.
I asked myself, "What is this?" After that, Prophet T.B. Joshua told me to stand up and walk
and because I had faith, I received healing from God; I started to run!
When Prophet T.B. Joshua came to me and touched my body, I felt like a lightning coming through my body
and when he told me to walk and run, I had the faith that I could then run
so as you see in the video, I was able to run.
Indeed we saw you running to the glory of God, after the prayer of Prophet T.B. Joshua,
and you are here today standing without your brace and without any walking aid.
How are you feeling now?
South Korea Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Testimony Time
Now, I am very well. I have no doubts about the healing I have received.
Now, I no longer need the leg brace and can move around freely.
Hallelujah!
South Korea Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Testimony Time
Right now, I feel very good.
Also, as you can see, I don't need my leg brace anymore.
I also have the faith that this healing will remain forever.
I can now do a lot of things that I could not do before.
Amen! Glory be to God!
Let's clap for Jesus Christ!
And there you can see her jogging - doing what she could not do before.
We would like you to walk in the midst of the children of God.
Just walk and show us that you are now healed to the glory of God.
There you can see her walking -
doing what she could not do before!
That is healing in the name of Jesus Christ!
She is here today without her brace, which is a clear evidence and proof
that Jesus Christ has healed her completely and effectually!
South Korea Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Testimony Time
You should not have an ounce of doubt that God can heal you.
Yesterday at the crusade, before the prayer, I said, "God, thank You for healing me".
Jesus heard my prayer and responded to me by providing my complete healing.
So, you too, don't lose hope; thank God for your healing before you even receive it.
South Korea Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Testimony Time
Praise the Lord! I want to tell you that you should not have doubt.
I already told God, "Thank You, Jesus, for healing me" before my healing.
If you have faith that God will heal you, then, you will be healed
If you are afraid of whether you will be healed, just tell God, "Thank You, Jesus, that you have healed me".
Amen. Let's clap for Jesus Christ!
South Korea Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Testimony Time
RV: Mel Flowers 25/03/2019